sup everyone Timbers went even faster
with a very severe today now I was
playing a game of Overwatch and and and
I rage quit and and I got so
suspended now no fog
I gotta say like I gotta be quacks I'm
aSleet and so I can't make too much
noise but but this is
messed up I bought the game I paid money
for it this is my game you can't ban me
that's no fair
no no I'm just saying I'm a game
developer I just released my game last
night as y'all know the legendary
prophecy of lying darkness the power to
save the world if you haven't bought it
go ahead in the description and and
I'll put a link to where you can buy for
only $10 only $10 and you get my entire
game better than this I'll tell you
that you can't get suspended for
ragequitting and that you
blizzard